Kevin Corlett

2309B Hickory St. ● St Louis, MO 63104 (314)413-4465 ● kevincorlett@outlook.com

Summary

Enthusiastic and hard-working professional with a passion for data and problemsolving. Eclectic background includes experience in B2B, Academia, retail, and non-profit. Curious, courteous, and collaborative by nature.

Development Skills

Languages - HTML • Java • JavaScript(ES6) • Typescript • Python

Backend - MySQL • Microsoft SQL Server • GraphQL • Spring • Node

Frontend - HTML• CSS • React.js • React Native • Redux • Apollo • Thymeleaf • Flask

Tools - IntelliJ• Webstorm • Git/GitHub • Expo • Atom • Vim

Work History

Union Machinery; Union, MO (2012-Present)

Director of Information and Marketing (Mike Lanham, Vice President – 636-583-3689)

<u>Primary Duties:</u> Spearheaded transition from Legacy ERP to a modern SQL database; Digital workflow design and training Systems Administration; General IT hardware oversight; Web and Social Media management. Secondary Duties: HR support; Account management; Bookkeeping, payroll, bank reconciliation.

University of Colorado (Boulder) Dept. of Theatre & Dance; Boulder, CO (2010-2012)

Graduate Teaching Assistant (Wendy Franz, graduate program coordinator - 303-492-7356)

Primary Duties: Grading papers; Preparing and delivering lectures for 100+ student Intro Level classes.

Secondary Duties: Research; Logistical support; Student meetings.

Pastoral Artisan Cheese Bread and Wine; Chicago IL (2008-2010)

Delivery Driver/Logistics Manager (Kelly Fallon-Wilson, supervisor - 773-472-4781)

<u>Primary duties:</u> Planning and executing the daily schedule of inventory transfers and deliveries (catering and wholesale) for a high-volume 3-location retail/catering/casual dining chain in downtown Chicago.

Secondary Duties: Sandwich bar; baked good production; retail floor; basic property maintenance.

Non-Profit

- •Circle of Concern Charity Golf Tournament Tournament Coordinator (2013-Present)
- •New Line Theatre Board Member (2012-Present)
- American Youth Foundation International Leadership Conference Community Coordinator (2003-2006)

Education

- •Launchcode Education (St. Louis, MO) LC101 graduate, Summer 2017
- Hanover College (Hanover, IN) Bachelor of Liberal Arts (Theatre Major, Political Science Minor)
- •University of Colorado at Boulder (Boulder, CO) 18 Hours post-graduate coursework
- Dale Carnegie Sales Success Training program graduate (Recipient of the Participation Award)

General Skillsets

Organizational management • Employee supervision and teambuilding • Problem solving/abstract thinking
Business Intelligence • Marketing and Branding • Media and Communications • Copy Writing and Editing
General Clerical Work (typing speed: 70 WPM) • Customer Service • Research • Public Speaking
Event Planning and Management • Budgeting and Accounting • Scheduling and Time Management